[Script Info]
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow:yes
[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhushi 1,方正准圆_GBK,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: LOGO,方正大标宋_GBK,72,&H001206C0,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: LOGO-2,方正大标宋_GBK,72,&H00000000,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,5,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: LOGO-3,方正大标宋_GBK,22,&H00F0ECEA,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: LOGO-B,方正大标宋_GBK,62,&H00000000,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: yuanhuan,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H000F0F0F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00AA55FF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo2,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H004080FF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo3,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H0040FF00,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo4,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H0000FFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo5,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H004646FF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo6,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00A600A6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo7,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FF80FF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.48,0:01:08.02,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}本字幕由雪酷字幕组制作 仅供交流 若您喜欢请支持购买正版
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.02,0:01:10.92,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}对字幕制作有任何建议 欢迎至雪酷论坛(http://bbs.sc-ol.com/)参与讨论
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.48,0:01:10.92,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}{\an2}翻译：最爱炮姐   后期：蝦條不脆
Dialogue: 1,0:00:01.25,0:00:05.62,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(92,130)}{\frx90\t(1,1800,1,\frx1)}雪酷
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.25,0:00:05.62,LOGO-2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(92,130)}{\frx90\t(1,1800,1,\frx1)}雪酷
Dialogue: 2,0:00:01.25,0:00:05.62,LOGO-3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(145,154)}{\frx90\t(1,1800,1,\frx1)}字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.09,0:00:05.62,LOGO-B,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx157.5\fscy238.75\frz300.299\pos(143,161)}{\fad(500,0)}）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.33,0:01:49.84,zhushi 1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(422,336)}{\fad(600,600)}逆袭的线索
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.56,0:01:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在地底深处的深处
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.08,0:01:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强制劳动设施召开的地下掷骰子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.69,0:01:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了击溃首次坐庄的开司
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.51,0:01:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长大槻与心腹石和
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.57,0:01:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各自下注两万
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.69,0:01:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司 关键局
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.66,0:01:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石和 456 赢两倍
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.75,0:01:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大槻 全色 赢三倍
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.13,0:01:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司昏倒 朝着负债地狱突入
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.48,0:01:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过了25天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.25,0:02:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了各位 久等的发薪日到了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.73,0:02:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位一个月以来辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.93,0:02:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.99,0:02:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个月一次
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.46,0:02:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照耀到这个看不到未来的地下生活中
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.44,0:02:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小小的治愈之光
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.81,0:02:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是对开司来说 却是沉重的警告之日
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.78,0:02:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警告他现在的处境
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.33,0:02:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让各位久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.98,0:02:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,45组的各位
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.93,0:02:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括开司在内的这6个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.33,0:02:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你 北川先生 辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.31,0:03:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿到的工资是两个月后的预支薪水
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.74,0:03:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里是减去了班长手续费之后的金额
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.45,0:03:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是正规金额九万一千的一半都不到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.22,0:03:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四万五千倍利卡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.05,0:03:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一个都是和开司一样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.84,0:03:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为赌博堕入负债地狱 只能拿到四万五千的男人们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.20,0:03:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括开司的这六个人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.34,0:03:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们鄙视地称呼他们为…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.38,0:03:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,45组
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.57,0:03:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了 开司
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.02,0:03:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.95,0:03:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也需要预支吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.04,0:03:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 只要把这薪水扔到他脸上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.67,0:03:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下个月再继续不拿薪水的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.92,0:03:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欠债的就还清
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.77,0:03:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要忍耐两个月 忍耐两个月…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.97,0:03:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啤酒很冰喔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.76,0:03:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五千倍利卡五千倍利卡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.20,0:04:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰的很凉喔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.63,0:04:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐两个月
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.20,0:04:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的开司没有这种毅力
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.66,0:04:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经看不到了 远去的希望
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.87,0:04:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一日外出券
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.53,0:04:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 本来要存五十万就是不可能的事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.12,0:04:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且那个外出券有附加条款
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.55,0:04:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有组织认可的人才能购买
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.88,0:04:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上头不可能会认可刚进来不久的我出去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.40,0:04:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正本来就办不到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.74,0:04:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且就算能出去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.23,0:04:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一千万那么大一笔钱也不是一天就能赚得到的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.40,0:05:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为自身心灵的软弱 逃避现实 催眠自己
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.20,0:05:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就是不现实 不可能实现的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.73,0:05:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是梦幻 绝对不可能实现的梦幻
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.49,0:05:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果我还是只能工作
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.58,0:05:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个地狱工作十五年
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.12,0:05:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.46,0:05:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.12,0:05:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.21,0:05:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.84,0:05:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.00,0:05:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前田 抬他到病房去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.52,0:05:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.89,0:05:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司 你也来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.93,0:05:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.69,0:05:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.57,0:05:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能工作
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.68,0:05:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还能工作
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.27,0:05:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是第一次到这里来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.31,0:06:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.48,0:06:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.78,0:06:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 不要把我带到那里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.73,0:06:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还能工作 还能工作…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.02,0:06:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生 有急诊病人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.68,0:06:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呈现在开司面前的是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.50,0:06:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地狱中的地狱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.39,0:06:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫人窒息的光景
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.69,0:06:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被粉尘伤了肺 搞坏了身体的人们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.45,0:06:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,败者组的末路
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.97,0:06:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.93,0:06:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扔那吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.91,0:06:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会我会给他找个地方躺着的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.03,0:06:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去似乎没有接受什么正规的治疗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.20,0:06:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为药很贵嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.11,0:06:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很贵…还需要钱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.72,0:07:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.03,0:07:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能会有钱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.83,0:07:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体一搞坏哪里来钱…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.93,0:07:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以有七八成都回不来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.91,0:07:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦身体搞坏了就完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.32,0:07:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我们来说
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.07,0:07:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.14,0:07:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.77,0:07:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.30,0:07:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.72,0:07:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到存够五十万为止
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.27,0:07:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消灭欲望 到外面去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.92,0:07:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是短短一星期就动摇的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.05,0:07:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相反的涌入脑中的是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.01,0:07:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导致破产的欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.51,0:07:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻欢作乐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.48,0:08:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈的 我不管了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.13,0:08:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想朝着欲望之海一跃而下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.31,0:08:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想堕落
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.04,0:08:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要随波逐流 朝着破灭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.49,0:08:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起加油吧 不能在这里花钱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.66,0:08:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩几小时了对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.75,0:08:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩几小时？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.44,0:08:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也和开司兄想法一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.60,0:08:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.53,0:08:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愿望是一日外出券 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.11,0:08:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.26,0:08:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且想要在今晚大赢特赢去买下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.09,0:08:35.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大赢特赢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.69,0:08:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掷骰子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.52,0:08:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个叫三好的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.07,0:08:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管目击了开司的遭遇
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.22,0:08:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是沉浸在首日赢钱的欢乐之中
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.70,0:08:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后也每次都参加赌局
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.48,0:08:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回过神来时已经过上了预支生活
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.84,0:08:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和开司一样 都是堕落到45组的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.69,0:08:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得今晚能赢 一定的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.77,0:09:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无药可救的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.91,0:09:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,软弱且好赌 而且又容易得意忘形
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.39,0:09:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔赢一把会高兴到极点 又立刻掉落
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.95,0:09:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,100%是失败者的类型
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.24,0:09:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起加油吧 开司兄
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.53,0:09:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会再赌博了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.28,0:09:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老老实实地存五十万
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.28,0:09:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您说什么呢 过着预支生活的我们想要存够五十万
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.67,0:09:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可要八个月啊八个月
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.41,0:09:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是办不到的 因为意志薄弱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.71,0:09:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司兄刚才不就差点顶不住了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.34,0:09:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才一个星期呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.55,0:09:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想要获得外出券就只能靠赌了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.38,0:09:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我特别告诉你一个好情报
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.13,0:09:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来的花色有几个倾向
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.88,0:09:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三好把他参加的所有赌局都仔细地记了下来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.82,0:09:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参考这个数据 寻找胜利的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.02,0:10:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是结果是大败 连败
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.92,0:10:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不就说明花色的数据也是没有意义的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.07,0:10:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 看看这里就能明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.78,0:10:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个ハ 就是班长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.23,0:10:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长花色总是很强
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.72,0:10:18.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也并不是无懈可击
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.57,0:10:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 比如这里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.02,0:10:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.16,0:10:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…你做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.76,0:10:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是偶然吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.10,0:10:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大槻掷出好花色时
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.96,0:10:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两旁必定会有石和跟沼川在
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.35,0:10:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我输的那晚也是一样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.34,0:10:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.62,0:10:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贯穿开司大脑的疑念
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.98,0:10:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骰子是立方体
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.68,0:10:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以无论是这样看 还是这样看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.28,0:10:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.18,0:10:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疑念转为确信
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.76,0:11:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本不是偶然
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.04,0:11:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.38,0:11:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.45,0:11:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司兄
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.96,0:11:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.65,0:11:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.10,0:11:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅 绝对不饶了他
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.31,0:11:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可真是杰作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.89,0:11:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,揍他又能怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.12,0:11:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使打他骂他
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.44,0:11:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也改变不了任何事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.60,0:11:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改变不了任何事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.92,0:12:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一周的周六大槻班开局
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.28,0:12:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算那混蛋的手法就如我想象的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.40,0:12:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算当场抓到他出千
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.13,0:12:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也会狡辩说是第一次 一时贪心之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.05,0:12:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最多只能让那局输双倍
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.52,0:12:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像他这种阴险狡猾的人怎么能那么轻易就放过他呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.78,0:12:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要给他更致命…更毁灭性的打击
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.34,0:12:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么做才好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.70,0:12:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么做…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.41,0:12:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在脑中急速展开的思考
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.58,0:12:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.27,0:12:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突破口的线索
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.57,0:12:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能行 这样一定能打倒大槻
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.65,0:13:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是要完全击溃他靠一个人是不够的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.44,0:13:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人数 人数要多
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.64,0:13:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司走向的是 45组的人们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.00,0:13:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚也赌输 穷光蛋底层败者组
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.33,0:13:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越看你们越像败者组
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.72,0:13:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照照镜子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.45,0:13:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个个都是典型的废物
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.08,0:13:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看样子就是人渣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.65,0:13:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一辈子都无法翻身的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.77,0:13:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷不丁的说什么呢混账
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.57,0:13:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司兄
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.55,0:13:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.35,0:13:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.79,0:13:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等察觉到时已经在人生的角落 社会的一角
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.25,0:13:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里就是我的指定席
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.57,0:13:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不被别人认同 被轻视 被厌恶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.38,0:13:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为忍受不了这些 堕落再堕落
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.92,0:14:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管在学校还是社会 都持续着堕落的人生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.77,0:14:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直落到这地底
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.72,0:14:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.20,0:14:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算在这里也还是败者组吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.04,0:14:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这地底深处还是要输吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.13,0:14:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为是同伴的班长把我们当成猎物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.38,0:14:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回过神来薪水的一半已经被剥削了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.42,0:14:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么 未免太蠢了一点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.79,0:14:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 大家也都听说过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.55,0:14:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长他们卖啤酒和下酒菜
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.98,0:14:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,产生的利益是和帝爱对半分的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.39,0:14:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加上他从我们这里剥削去的钱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.14,0:14:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们认为每个月会有多少钱进班长的口袋？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.76,0:14:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粗略计算一下 大概是七十二万
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.05,0:14:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七 七十…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.37,0:14:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.69,0:14:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老老实实每个月存九万存半年以上简直太蠢了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.46,0:14:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大槻一定会这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.74,0:15:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「简直是疯了」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.50,0:15:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不停的养肥大槻他们 我们则是他们的粮食
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.91,0:15:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样你们满足吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.67,0:15:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.65,0:15:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在才来说这种事根本屁用没有
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.25,0:15:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 开司兄 又有什么办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.10,0:15:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就甘心继续当败者组吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.94,0:15:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是败者组
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.02,0:15:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 你就是败者组
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.14,0:15:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对不对不对 我不想听
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.56,0:15:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 别理这种家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.05,0:15:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.48,0:15:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会给你们看的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.85,0:15:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.94,0:15:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把通往胜利的道路展现给你们看的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.65,0:15:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道路？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.79,0:15:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打倒班长大槻 赚大钱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.93,0:15:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要赢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.16,0:15:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.71,0:15:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么做？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.73,0:16:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么赢大钱？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.60,0:16:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只此一次 我让你们见识一下奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.76,0:16:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇迹？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.59,0:16:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大槻有个倾向
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.00,0:16:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当场子沸腾 在关键时刻
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.32,0:16:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会有特别好运的倾向
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.68,0:16:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拼了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.26,0:16:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.29,0:16:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.70,0:16:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.37,0:16:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 我只说一次
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.76,0:16:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么一次 我来猜班长的花色
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.06,0:16:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事怎么可能办…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.34,0:16:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花色是456
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.73,0:16:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.37,0:16:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思啊各位 是456
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.88,0:16:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.21,0:16:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜中了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.92,0:16:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢两倍 赌博真是可怕呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.82,0:17:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说 他出老千了？！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.72,0:17:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王八蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.30,0:17:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.72,0:17:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.03,0:17:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还用问嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.20,0:17:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,揍他一顿让他坦白出千的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.21,0:17:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不行 不能那么轻易放过他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.84,0:17:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你 那你准备怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.02,0:17:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别问了 先坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.23,0:17:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实他的强运并非偶然而是有理由的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.46,0:17:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 那同时也是致命的漏洞
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.51,0:17:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就攻击那里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.13,0:17:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是机会只有一次
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.34,0:17:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然真的只有一次
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.37,0:17:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但可以用奇袭击溃他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.69,0:17:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一直以来被人利用至今的我们
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.28,0:17:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到手的千载难逢 最初也是最后的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.73,0:17:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果现在不能崛起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.39,0:17:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今后一生都是奴隶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.47,0:18:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三万 这是我现在全部家产
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.02,0:18:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也把身上有的钱都拿出来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.41,0:18:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身上…全部？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.37,0:18:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 反正你们也跟身无分文没什么两样了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.99,0:18:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.77,0:18:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这点了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.99,0:18:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会拿出来的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.69,0:18:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收集来的钱 是45组败者组六个人身上仅有的一点钱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.83,0:18:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少得可怜的命脉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.86,0:18:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5…6…7
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.33,0:18:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合计62700
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.07,0:18:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后三个月 我们要靠这些钱挺过去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.75,0:18:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺过去？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.57,0:18:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 要限制吃喝
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.23,0:18:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,禁止喝酒 香烟每天一根
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.41,0:19:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赌博是绝对不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.53,0:19:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要尽量节约还清欠债
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.57,0:19:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到能拿到全部薪水九万的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.17,0:19:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就用那笔钱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.53,0:19:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干掉大槻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.14,0:19:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小钱是干不掉他的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.57,0:19:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最多让他吓一跳就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.36,0:19:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样可不行 要全力以赴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.75,0:19:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用我们所能达到的最大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.65,0:19:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 差不多该赢一把了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.04,0:19:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放上来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.43,0:19:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参加这最初也是最后的奇袭 最终战略的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.81,0:19:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把手叠在我的手上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.81,0:19:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 大钱就是指…可以去外面的金额吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.41,0:19:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.33,0:19:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.94,0:19:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能去外面…能去外面的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.04,0:20:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我参加
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.20,0:20:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.44,0:20:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只拿出了1300…也可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.85,0:20:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.62,0:20:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我今年已经42岁了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.91,0:20:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.40,0:20:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.99,0:20:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参加
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.08,0:20:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参加
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.60,0:20:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也…让我也参加吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.55,0:20:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差一人 你准备怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.65,0:20:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.57,0:20:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是个吊儿郎当的人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.82,0:20:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直吊儿郎当 得过且过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.34,0:20:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游手好闲 拖拖拉拉的过着日子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.09,0:20:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过其实…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.67,0:20:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在等待…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.29,0:20:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一天 能够崛起的契机
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.77,0:20:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭我一个人无论如何都办不到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.94,0:20:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这次…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.37,0:21:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起崛起吧 前田兄
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.33,0:21:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起来 获得胜利吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.17,0:21:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,45组 集结
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.75,0:21:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,败家犬之中的败者组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.36,0:21:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些身处底层中的底层的男人们
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.46,0:21:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在将手叠在一起站了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.92,0:21:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了打倒大槻！！
