[Script Info]
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow:yes
[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,0,0,5,1
Style: zhushi 1,方正准圆_GBK,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,5,0,0,0,1
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,0,0,5,1
Style: LOGO,方正大标宋_GBK,72,&H001206C0,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: LOGO-2,方正大标宋_GBK,72,&H00000000,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,5,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: LOGO-3,方正大标宋_GBK,22,&H00F0ECEA,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: LOGO-B,方正大标宋_GBK,62,&H00000000,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: yuanhuan,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H000F0F0F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H000000FF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo2,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H000000FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo3,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H000000FF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo4,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H0000FFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo5,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H004646FF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo6,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00A600A6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: luosuo7,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FF80FF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.48,0:01:10.92,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}本字幕由雪酷字幕组制作 仅供交流 若您喜欢请支持购买正版
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.48,0:01:10.92,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}对字幕制作有任何建议 欢迎至雪酷论坛(http://bbs.sc-ol.com/)参与讨论
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.48,0:01:10.92,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}{\an2}翻译：最爱炮姐   后期：蝦條不脆
Dialogue: 1,0:00:01.25,0:00:05.62,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(92,130)}{\frx90\t(1,1800,1,\frx1)}雪酷
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.25,0:00:05.62,LOGO-2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(92,130)}{\frx90\t(1,1800,1,\frx1)}雪酷
Dialogue: 2,0:00:01.25,0:00:05.62,LOGO-3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(145,154)}{\frx90\t(1,1800,1,\frx1)}字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.09,0:00:05.62,LOGO-B,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx157.5\fscy238.75\frz300.299\pos(143,161)}{\fad(500,0)}）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.68,0:01:36.44,zhushi 1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(425,330)}{\fad(500,500)}强运的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.83,0:01:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愤怒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.62,0:01:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愤怒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.18,0:01:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愤怒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.02,0:01:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这样就好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.53,0:01:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是赌博
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.30,0:01:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司沉睡着的本能
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.25,0:01:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被点燃了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.56,0:01:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从旁人看来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.20,0:01:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只会认为开司的押注是在自暴自弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.61,0:01:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上 钱就像开闸的水一样流走 开司在不断地下沉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.99,0:01:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是与此同时 开司体内的某些什么正在觉醒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:01:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就赌那个「觉醒」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.93,0:02:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使不断在下沉 也继续押注三千
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.02,0:02:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热血沸腾地押注了40分钟后
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.72,0:02:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司再次做出决断
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.27,0:02:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续增加倍利卡 首次押注五千！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.99,0:02:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后终于 得到了回报
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.24,0:02:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.18,0:02:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,456 赢两倍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.10,0:02:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了 开司的热血
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.77,0:02:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于得到了正面的回报
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.93,0:02:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好运降临 这一注就进账一万
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.49,0:02:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下沉到了两万八千的开司 复活
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.18,0:02:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到了三万八千
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.86,0:02:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 轮到了坐庄
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.48,0:02:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了 就是现在 现在不做更待何时
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.19,0:03:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坐庄 下注吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.56,0:03:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.95,0:03:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 看到势头正旺的开司
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.18,0:03:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个个全都下了小注
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.05,0:03:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不奋力一搏 全部都是小注
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.88,0:03:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得很难受吧 开司
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.40,0:03:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得在势头正旺时接下了庄
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.64,0:03:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是大家退缩的心情我也能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.47,0:03:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真头疼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.68,0:03:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 没办法 我来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.72,0:03:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了给开司的首次庄家讨个好彩头
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.19,0:03:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,押个大注当红包吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.05,0:03:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两万倍利卡？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.96,0:03:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.73,0:03:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.45,0:04:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在等这一刻吗 等着我坐庄
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.31,0:04:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后准备一口气将我击溃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.47,0:04:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人都押了两万 赌注总计四万
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.62,0:04:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我手头上只有三万八
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.05,0:04:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果输了可给不出四万
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.92,0:04:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来 自然就要欠债
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.70,0:04:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,债上加债
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.09,0:04:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,负债地狱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.30,0:04:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 不好意思呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.19,0:04:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本想搞热一下气氛的这下反而有些冷场了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.01,0:04:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过就像我一开始说明的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.80,0:04:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人两万是这个赌场正规的上限
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.29,0:04:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有任何问题
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.53,0:04:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真要说有问题也是在之后
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.45,0:04:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果开司赢了就什么问题都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.07,0:04:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是万一输了的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.93,0:05:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据我的计算 开司现在手上不足四万
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.77,0:05:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.47,0:05:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.09,0:05:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为了一会不引起争执
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.73,0:05:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得把地下的规矩向你说明一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.02,0:05:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说白了 就是欠债
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.48,0:05:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预支薪水的规定
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.08,0:05:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果开司输了 需要付四万的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.35,0:05:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以强制性预支你的薪水来还债
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.30,0:05:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后才是问题所在
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.35,0:05:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为开司已经预支了下个月的薪水
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.75,0:05:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以要预支的话 就要预支下下个月的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.54,0:05:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 下个月或许开司就会因为无法承受沉重的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.49,0:05:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑到你会病倒的风险…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.43,0:05:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这次不是支付你全部薪水的九万而是六万
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.58,0:06:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那下下个月的预支自然我们就得更小心一点了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.80,0:06:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不好开口 不过我还是得狠下心来告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.66,0:06:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下下个月的预支是九万的一半
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.05,0:06:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预支给开司的薪水 四万五千
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.20,0:06:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 这里的各位都已经认可了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.62,0:06:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要怪我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.75,0:06:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 我真是看错你了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.31,0:06:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个了不起的恶棍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.22,0:06:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说出来都不害臊 什么六万啊四万五千的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.09,0:06:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己制定这些让人陷入泥沼地狱的规定
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.30,0:06:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说大家都认可了！？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.17,0:06:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻不傻啊 想逃脱这种预支生活的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.83,0:06:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就必须连续两个月忍受没有薪水的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.59,0:06:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这种事在尝过禁果之后是无法办到的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.01,0:06:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使觉得不合理 在发薪日那天估计还是会接受
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.23,0:07:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后永远永远拿着…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.88,0:07:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一半的四万五千
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.25,0:07:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不就是剥削吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.36,0:07:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在回想起来 你送我的那一小罐啤酒就是为了这个
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.56,0:07:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先刺激猎物的欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.76,0:07:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让其花钱 最后再将其拖入这个赌局中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.59,0:07:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世上就是有你这种人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.23,0:07:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在地下一起工作 同样被逼入绝境的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.93,0:07:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连这些同伴的辛苦钱都要据为己有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.73,0:07:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸走大家的血汗钱 你简直就跟水蛭一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.38,0:07:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤脑筋啊 我是为了大家的方便所提供的服务
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.72,0:07:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却遭到了这种冤枉的指责
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.02,0:07:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司 就算我是照顾大家起居的班长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.42,0:08:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我也不能白白付出吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.73,0:08:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总要追求一点回报的 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.98,0:08:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快掷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.67,0:08:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庄家不掷赌局就无法开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.08,0:08:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么呢 只要开司你赢了就没有任何问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.46,0:08:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们早就知道了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.95,0:08:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次的赌局就是为了坑我而设的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.80,0:08:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旁边的新人三好暂且不说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.41,0:08:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人肯定都是知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.71,0:08:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明知道却还什么都不说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.18,0:08:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实事情很简单
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.50,0:08:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家虽说不是出于自愿 但还是协助了班长
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.52,0:08:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实都对班长的霸权感到不满 不平
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.53,0:08:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但又害怕自己被盯上 出于无奈只能协助
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.10,0:08:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最恨你们这种人了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.21,0:09:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长固然可恨 不过像你们这种墙头草也无法原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.42,0:09:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会输啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.23,0:09:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要赢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.87,0:09:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里 在这里获得胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.43,0:09:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能输
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.87,0:09:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天地之别 输赢简直是天地之别
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.28,0:09:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是输了 在这个地底深处都逃脱不了被剥削的命运
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.92,0:09:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薪水的一半都会被榨走
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.32,0:09:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和奴隶一样 沉没
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.27,0:09:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会这么沉下去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.81,0:09:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是只要赢了 赢了就有四万
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.01,0:09:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我手上全部就有七万八千
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.25,0:09:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来还掉班长那里六万 还能剩下一万八千
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.55,0:09:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够重头来过 希望能够再次点燃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.49,0:09:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,获得一日外出券的希望
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.68,0:09:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就凭这一掷的花色
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.80,0:10:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈的…妈的…妈的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.29,0:10:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我总是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.63,0:10:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮到我的总是这种角色
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.22,0:10:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之所以会来到这个地下地狱
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.28,0:10:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底就是因为没有能够拒绝当别人的担保人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.17,0:10:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且来到地狱之后 还要成为这些家伙的猎物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.32,0:10:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈的！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.25,0:10:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花色5
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.32,0:10:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 还不错
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.75,0:10:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 现在我风头正旺
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.77,0:10:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会出现什么太烂的点数
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.96,0:10:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个结果也是当然的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.31,0:10:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本打算击溃我 却自掘坟墓了呢 班长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.50,0:10:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 在掷骰子里的花色5
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.93,0:10:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经相当大了 算很不错
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.62,0:10:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现花色的几率 除了全色和456之外
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.91,0:11:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管哪个数字都一样 都是108分之15
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.31,0:11:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能赢5的只有6
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.18,0:11:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现1-4的几率是出现6的四倍
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.36,0:11:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加上没点的话 几率还会更高
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.04,0:11:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5可以说是有九成胜率的花色
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.80,0:11:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上 连三好在内的三人都输给了开司的5
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.64,0:11:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三连败
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.68,0:11:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于轮到了下注两万的两人之一
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.31,0:11:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碗到了班长派的石和手中
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.77,0:11:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对开司来说其他人怎么都好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.78,0:11:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是班长大槻和这个男人的点数
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.64,0:11:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石和 注目的第一掷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.46,0:11:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花色4
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.88,0:11:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.48,0:11:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好很好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.77,0:11:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先拿下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.98,0:11:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.36,0:12:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是班长大槻
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.51,0:12:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别出现 绝对不能出现
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.35,0:12:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能出现5以上的点数
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.65,0:12:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是4
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.41,0:12:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长阵营两连败
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.56,0:12:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太…太…太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.40,0:12:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢啦赢啦赢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.31,0:12:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司兄
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.44,0:12:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 我活下来了 活下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.26,0:12:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我赢了 复活了 复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.74,0:12:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于从欠债的压榨地狱中爬上来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.58,0:12:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下又有希望了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.92,0:12:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有希望冲刺那个一日外出券
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.11,0:12:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.25,0:12:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长在大额赌注时输了真是少见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.29,0:13:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果 包括沼川在内 班长阵营三连败
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.57,0:13:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后的闲家也都没有能够赢过开司的5
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.80,0:13:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司 这次庄家全胜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.96,0:13:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思啊各位 不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.63,0:13:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不客气了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.92,0:13:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.84,0:13:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一轮就赢到了四万两千两百
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.84,0:13:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来输到现在 全靠这一把就逆转了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.25,0:13:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至还有赚
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.35,0:13:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了八万 就算还掉六万的欠债 还能剩下两万
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.55,0:14:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算班长再怎么想击溃我 只要撑过庄就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.11,0:14:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为闲家能够控制押多少注
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.35,0:14:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还掉预支的六万 能生还了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.17,0:14:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.37,0:14:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庄要做两次
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.21,0:14:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家不都是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.18,0:14:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有花色1 没点 123才可以只做一次庄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.93,0:14:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要装迷糊 把碗给别人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.48,0:14:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对喔 不好意思 一不小心犯迷糊了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.43,0:14:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 不是装的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.39,0:14:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下注吧 我现在丝毫不觉得自己会输
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.93,0:14:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管一次还是两次都一样 下注吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.87,0:14:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长他们 又各自下了两万 总计四万
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.19,0:14:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来真的吗 就那么想把我一举击溃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.99,0:14:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里哪里 才不是击溃什么的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.21,0:14:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是觉得你的运气差不多也该走下坡路了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.63,0:15:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么蠢话 你的眯眯眼还在发光呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.05,0:15:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本就是一心想击溃我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.03,0:15:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过不好意思啊 你判断失误了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.70,0:15:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那些钱就跟送我没两样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.61,0:15:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该还能掷出大点数
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.28,0:15:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得不会了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.53,0:15:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快下注吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.36,0:15:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别拖时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.82,0:15:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.43,0:15:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定能掷出来的 一定能
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.40,0:15:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.93,0:15:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我掷的话 能出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.31,0:15:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在掷一定能出大点数
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.89,0:15:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我掷了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.96,0:15:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.98,0:16:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司两掷 全部没点
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.09,0:16:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看吧 差不多运势已经退潮了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.10,0:16:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.58,0:16:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个骰子的点数组合
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.51,0:16:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部有216种
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.29,0:16:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中包括123在内
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.25,0:16:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掷骰子一共有108种有点的花色
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.74,0:16:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说掷一次出花色的几率正好是50%
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.67,0:16:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掷三次出现花色几率又会大大提高
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.31,0:16:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有87.5%
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.90,0:16:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说掷三次的话 有接近九成的几率会有花色
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.63,0:16:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 出现吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.33,0:16:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决定光明与黑暗的第三掷
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.52,0:16:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 是6 是6啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.74,0:16:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我赢了 太好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.79,0:17:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得救了 在最后的最后
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.32,0:17:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被强运的流向 碎片给救了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.17,0:17:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了太好了太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.07,0:17:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.82,0:17:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不一定赢呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.67,0:17:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也还有一定的胜算呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.30,0:17:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜算？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.52,0:17:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 通常的掷骰子在掷出6之后就结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.10,0:17:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庄家通吃
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.89,0:17:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闲家没有掷骰子的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.70,0:17:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这里是有机会的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.00,0:17:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能掷 不管几率多小 胜算还是有的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.55,0:17:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果和开司一样是花色6就是平手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.78,0:17:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能出456或者全色还能逆转
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.78,0:17:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定反而还是我们赢 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.52,0:17:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有希望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.27,0:17:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？你真的这么想？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.33,0:18:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.07,0:18:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为事实就是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.00,0:18:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白痴 这种事不会发生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.74,0:18:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扔个几百次是能掷出456跟全色
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.37,0:18:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在现在 在这个瞬间是不会出现的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.49,0:18:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有可能那么碰巧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.58,0:18:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你其实心里也明白吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.86,0:18:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止已经有过不少次了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.66,0:18:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白的 开司你说的我也明白
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.64,0:18:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是怎么说呢 我还是相信
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.14,0:18:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人的念力有时可以左右点数
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.37,0:18:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,念力能够提高…起死回生的可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.73,0:18:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你说念力？！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.17,0:18:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.55,0:18:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种玩意鬼才明白啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.09,0:18:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太荒唐了 都不知道你在说些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.26,0:19:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还念力呀 厉害厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.87,0:19:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是太搞笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.53,0:19:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,念力…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.24,0:19:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实荒唐 可是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.47,0:19:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 班长阵营石和的第一掷
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.36,0:19:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,456 赢两倍
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.41,0:19:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好耶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.66,0:19:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两万的两倍是四万 你刚才那把就白赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.96,0:19:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手上的八万已经只剩四万了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.42,0:19:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.94,0:19:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会有这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.15,0:19:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后班长大槻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.41,0:20:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.44,0:20:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司 赌博真是可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.89,0:20:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的太可怕了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.40,0:20:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长大槻 居然是全色5！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.51,0:20:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢三倍 压倒性胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.28,0:20:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 这不可能 为什么会出现这种花色
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.10,0:20:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种荒唐的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.63,0:20:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司 不好意思 你破产了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.69,0:20:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全色是赢三倍 所以你要支付六万
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.73,0:20:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司手上的四万不够支付
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.69,0:21:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在负 两万！！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.16,0:21:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司兄 开司兄
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.81,0:21:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.37,0:21:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这种…这种没天理的事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.21,0:21:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老是发生在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.67,0:21:18.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开司昏厥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.96,0:21:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在地底深处的深处 还是朝着负债地狱突入！！
